<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Kevin Zhou</title>
    <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Kevin Zhou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://knzhou.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knzhou.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography I&amp;rsquo;m a graduate student interested in particle phenomenology, biophysics, and physics education. I&amp;rsquo;m currently spending two years in the UK as a Marshall scholar, and plan to begin a PhD at Stanford in 2019 funded by an NSF Graduate Research fellowship. A complete CV is available here.
I got started by devouring the scifi section of my local public library, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until watching Particle Fever in college that I knew what I wanted to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knzhou.github.io/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture Notes</title>
      <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/lectures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knzhou.github.io/home/lectures/</guid>
      <description>These are the notes I&amp;rsquo;ve taken while learning physics. They&amp;rsquo;re very compact and don&amp;rsquo;t usually correspond closely with any particular course; instead they&amp;rsquo;re packed full of all the neat things I&amp;rsquo;ve found reading books. Currently they weigh in at just over 400,000 words.
Undergraduate (MIT) These notes summarize undergraduate material. They roughly cover both the MIT undergraduate sequence and Part I and II of the Cambridge physics sequence.
 Undergraduate Physics Undergraduate Math Geometry and Topology Solid State Physics  Master&amp;rsquo;s (Cambridge, Oxford) These notes cover material taught at Cambridge&amp;rsquo;s Part III and Oxford&amp;rsquo;s MMathPhys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutoring</title>
      <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/tutoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knzhou.github.io/home/tutoring/</guid>
      <description>I offer tutoring for the USA Physics Olympiad (USAPhO) and the International Physics Olympiad (IPhO). I competed at the IPhO in 2012 and 2013 and taught at the US Physics Team training camp in 2015 through 2017.
The tutoring program is designed for students aiming for gold medals at the USAPhO or IPhO. It is based on learning by problem solving. During the training, students receive weekly handouts containing about 30 questions, which are discussed at an online meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knzhou.github.io/home/writing/</guid>
      <description>Learning A lot of people ask me for advice for learning physics or preparing for the F=ma and USAPhO exams. Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of what I know.
 Learning Introductory Physics. A FAQ for high school students who want to start learning physics or taking part in physics competitions. After Introductory Physics. Some advice for self-taught high school students on what to learn after mastering the basics.  Expository Below are some expository works on physics, at both the popular and technical level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knzhou.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m active (perhaps too active) on Physics StackExchange. If you want to chat, feel free to email or ping me in the h bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knzhou.github.io/home/talks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knzhou.github.io/home/posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://knzhou.github.io/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knzhou.github.io/home/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>